Do I and the European peoples of Russia
разве мне и европейские народы россии
European
европейский
European peoples of Russia there
европейские народы россии там
take Russia so now the Soviet Union of the
возьми россию так сейчас советский союз
Russian Empire is Asian and
российской империи это азии и
territorial in ethnic composition
территориальное по этническому составу
and actually not in terms of ethnic
ну и собственно не по этническому
composition for all peoples, look well,
составу по все народы смотри хорошо
is it for me in the winter European peoples of
разве мне на зимний европейские народы
Russia European
россии европейский
European peoples once there
европейские народы раз там
yes, you can name a lot of Asian
да вот азиатских это много назовешь
peoples of Russia and European,
народов россии и европейских
but the Germans are not there with such a nose, they were
но немцы не есть там таким от носом это
just settlements,
просто поселения были
yes, this settlement was just just
да это поселение просто были просто
settlers, that is, there is no German ethnic
поселенцы то есть нету этнической
territory,
территории
what
немецком что
are we looking at which of all the ethnic groups
такие вот смотрим какие из всех этносов
that inhabit compactly there the
которые населяют компактно там
territory of the Russian Federation  what
территорию российской федерации какие
Europeans
европейски
are good, look, well,
вот хорошо смотри-ка хорошо
come on, so that’s all Russian,
давай так вот весь российский
I don’t understand, look here in the Russian
я по не понимаю смотри вот в российской
Federation there are Russians so Russian is
федерации есть русские так русский это
European Slavs there are Tatars there are
европейский славяне есть татары есть
Chechens there are Dagestanis there are Khanty there are
чеченцы есть дагестанцы есть ханты есть
Mansi see all nations except Russians
манси смотри все народы кроме русских
it turns out Asia Asian Nars  odes like this
это получается азии азиатские народы так
in russia
в россии
not for everything there are no compact settlements
не на все нету компактные поселения у
we don’t have technical territories belgorod
нас нет технических территориях белгород
kuban
кубань
yes well we have a small amount of
да ну у нас есть небольшое количество
supply see yourself excuse yourself so
подачи смотрите себя отмазываешься чтобы
that in russia let’s
то по россии давайте
that is, don’t look by the number 2 by the
то есть не смотреть по количеству 2 по
number of people we understand that everything is
количеству народом мы понимаем что все
here tell me  besides the Russians, some
вот назови мне кроме русских какой-то
European people on the territory of Russia,
европейский народ на территории россии
some kind of typo, people’s map of Russia,
какой то я описка народная карта россии
you see, you say that
ты смотри ты говоришь что
Russia is Europe, they are Asian, and so on,
россия это европа они азии так и другого
see Khant Buryats, Khakasses, who are there yakut
смотри хант буряты хакасы кто там yakut
and these dalgans here, everything is Asian
и эти далгании тут все азиатским
from the Finns, yes, well, the Finns can
от финны можно да хорошо финам можно
attribute it to rubles scanda rather it’s on the
отнести к рублей сканда скорее это на
run ok there three peoples found European
бегу ok там три народа нашли европейский
further
дальше
no you just said that russia is
нет ты просто сказал что россия это
europe and not for its sake in russia it is both
европа а не ради нее в россии это и
geographically and in terms of the composition of the peoples it is
географически и по составу народов это
asia
азии